Finding Aid for the Norman Shannon Hall Papers LSC.0806
UCLA Library Special Collections
Norman Shannon Hall papers
1925-1960
UCLA Library Special Collections
Hall, Norman S. (Norman Shannon)
LSC.0806
5.5 Linear Feet (11 boxes)
This collection consists of 111 screenplays and 19 television plays by Norman Shannon Hall, and 17 items (plays, screenplays, and television plays) by friends of Hall. Among them are Robert Cedric Sheriff's The Road Back and Porter Emerson Browne's The Bad Man.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Norman Shannon Hall, May 1963.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942331063606533
Scope and Content
This collection consists of 111 screenplays and 19 television plays by Norman Shannon Hall, and 17 items (plays, screenplays, and television plays) by friends of Hall. Among them are Robert Cedric Sheriff's The Road Back, and Porter Emerson Browne's The Bad Man.
Plays.; Television plays.; Film scripts.; Television writers -- United States -- Archives.; Screenwriters -- United States -- Archives.; Hall, Norman S. (Norman Shannon)--Archives.
- Storm Over the Philippines, February 1945 (Box 1)
- California Joe, September 1943 (Box 1)
- San Antone Ambush, June 1949 (Box 1)
- Daredevils of the Sky, January 1948 (Box 1)
- Storm Over the Philippines, undated (Box 1)
- "Production #S-19", June 1942 (Box 1)
- "Production #S-20", August 1942 (Box 1)
- "Production #S-23", December 1942 (Box 1)
- "Production #S-24", February 1943 (Box 1)
- The Fabulous Texan, 1945 (Box 2)
- "Production #1307", May 1943 (Box 2)
- "Production #1309", October 1943 (Box 2)
- "Production #1412", April 1944 (Box 2)
- South of Rio, April 1949 (Box 2)
- Montana Belle, October 1948 (Box 2)
- Slippy McGee, August 1947 (Box 2)
- Rose of the Yukon, July 1948 (Box 2)
- "Production S-25", March 1943 (Box 2)
- "Production S-26", March 1943 (Box 2)
- Drums of Fu Manchu, December 1939 (Box 3)
- The Adventures of Red Ryder, Episode One: Murder on the Santa Fe Trail, March 1940 (Box 3)
- King of the Royal Mounted, June 1940 (Box 3)
- Mysterious Doctor Satan, September 1940 (Box 3)
- Captain Marvel, Episode One: Curse of the Scorpion, December 1940 (Box 3)
- Jungle Girl, Episode One: Death by Voodoo, March 1941 (Box 3)
- King of the Texas Rangers, Episode One: The Fifth Column Strikes, May 1941 (Box 3)
- Spy Smasher, Episode One: America Beware!, December 1941 (Box 3)
- Untitled Roy Rogers, January 1938 (Box 3)
- Sheriff of Las Vegas, July 1944 (Box 3)
- Sundown in Santa Fe, August 1948 (Box 3)
- Law of the Golden West, January 1949 (Box 3)
- Rose of the Yukon, March 1948 (Box 3)
- "Production #S-27", July 1943 (Box 3)
- The San Antonio Kid, February 1944 (Box 4)
- Vigilantes of Dodge City, May 1944 (Box 4)
- Sheriff of Las Vegas, July 1944 (Box 4)
- Outlaws of Santa Fe, October 1943 (Box 4)
- "Production #S-31", December 1943 (Box 4)
- Sheriff of Sundown, May 1944 (Box 4)
- Rhythm of the Saddle, undated (Box 4)
- Arizona Terror, October 1941 (Box 4)
- Red River Renegades, March 1946 (Box 4)
- Untitled Sunset Carson, April 1946 (Box 4)
- Fort Dodge Stampede, January 1949 (Box 4)
- Law of the Golden West, January 1949 (Box 4)
- South of Rio, April 1949 (Box 4)
- Law of the Golden West, January 1949 (Box 4)
- Untitled (Variety), August 1948 (Box 4)
- The Kid from Hangtown by Doris Schroeder, April 1942 (Box 5)
- "Production #S-19", May 1942 (Box 5)
- Dead Man's Gulch, September 1942 (Box 5)
- Untitled Barry, November 1942 (Box 5)
- Days of Old Cheyenne, December 1942 (Box 5)
- Bad Man of Sonora, February 1943 (Box 5)
- Sundown in Santa Fe, August 1948 (Box 5)
- The Vanishing Westerner, November 1948 (Box 5)
- San Antone Ambush, June 1949 (Box 5)
- "Production #S-21", September 1942 (Box 5)
- "Production #S-23", December 1942 (Box 5)
- Carson City Cyclone, December 1942 (Box 5)
- Days of Old Cheyenne, September 1943 (Box 5)
- "Production #S-24", January 1943 (Box 5)
- Montana Belle, October 1948 (Box 5)
- Slippy McGee, August 1946 (Box 5)
- Corpus Christi Bandits, December 1944 (Box 6)
- Sheriff of Sun-Down, May 1944 (Box 6)
- California Joe, September 1943 (Box 6)
- "Production #1412", April 1944 (Box 6)
- "Production A-402", April 1944 (Box 6)
- Cheyenne Wildcat, May 1944 (Box 6)
- Flame of the Barbary Coast, June 1944 (Box 6)
- Yankee Doodle Cowboy, October 1938 (Box 6)
- The Frontier Express, December 1938 (Box 6)
- Storm Over the Philippines, November 1944 (Box 6)
- Pack Train, September 1952 (Box 7)
- Night Stage to Galveston, July 1951 (Box 7)
- The Horse Soldiers, September 1958 (Box 7)
- Beyond the Purple Hills (Valley of Fires), September 1949 (Box 7)
- Indian Territory, November 1949 (Box 7)
- Whirlwind, October 1950 (Box 7)
- Last Days of Boot Hill, April 1947 (Box 7)
- Winning of the West, June 1952 (Box 7)
- Gene Autry and the Mounties, May 1950 (Box 7)
- Blazing Across the Pecos, August 1947 (Box 7)
- Whirlwind Raiders, June 1947 (Box 8)
- Texans Never Cry, June 1950 (Box 8)
- Beyond the Purple Hills (Valley of Fire), September 1949 (Box 8)
- Blue Canadian Rockies, April 1952 (Box 8)
- The Missouri Traveler, April 1957 (Box 8)
- Apache Country, October 1951 (Box 8)
- The Missouri Traveler, March 1957 (Box 8)
- The Missouri Traveler, undated (Box 8)
- Whirlwind, October 1950 (Box 9)
- Blazing Through Cimarron, February 1947 (Box 9)
- Renegade Canyon, February 1953 (Box 9)
- Three Lovers, undated (Box 9)
- The Young Land, July 1957 (Box 9)
- The Young Land, August 1957 (Box 9)
- Marked Bullets (Range Rider Series), undated (Box 10)
- Annie Trusts a Convict (Annie Oakley Series), undated (Box 10)
- Annie Finds Strange Treasure (Annie Oakley Series), undated (Box 10)
- Trails Westward (The Adventures of Kit Carson), undated (Box 10)
- Trails to Bordertown (The Adventures of Kit Carson), undated (Box 10)
- Annie Trusts a Convict (Annie Oakley Series), undated (Box 10)
- Annie Helps a Drifter (Annie Oakley), undated (Box 10)
- Annie Meets Some Tenderfeet (Annie Oakley), undated (Box 10)
- Annie Gets Her Man (Annie Oakley Series), undated (Box 10)
- Heritage of the Mounties (King of the Royal Mounted Series), January 1956 (Box 10)
- Six-shooter Sweepstakes, undated (Box 10)
- Greed Rides the Range, undated (Box 10)
- The Western Way, undated (Box 10)
- Hold Up, undated (Box 10)
- Heritage of the Mounties (King of the Royal Mounted Series), 1956 (Box 10)
- The Brand Inspector, undated (Box 10)
- The Wrong Dead Man, undated (Box 10)
- Flint and Steel (Annie Oakley Series), 1956 (Box 10)
- Rawhide: Incident of Fear in the Streets, 1959 (Box 11)
- Rawhide: Incident of the Roman Candles, 1959 (Box 11)
- Tales of the Texas Rangers: Ransom Fight, June 1955 (Box 11)
- Tales of the Texas Rangers: Blazing Across the Pecos, August 1955 (Box 11)
- Tales of the Texas Rangers: Buckaroo from Powder River, September 1955 (Box 11)
- Tales of the Texas Rangers: Last Days of Boot Hill, 1955 (Box 11)
- Tales of the Texas Rangers: Trail Herd, 1956 (Box 11)
- Tales of the Texas Rangers: A Texas Million, 1957 (Box 11)
- Tales of the Texas Rangers: Panhandle, 1957 (Box 11)
- Tales of the Texas Rangers: Whirlwind Raiders, 1957 (Box 11)
- The Bad Man by Porter Emerson Browne, undated (Box 11)
- The Road Back by R.C. Sheriff, December 1936 (Box 11)
- Frontier Frenzy by Frank Nugent, 1936 (Box 11)